KIANOOSH SOLEIMANI

REACT JS AND NEXT JS DEVELOPER

Personal information

**** 09395043237

mazyar.solo@gmail.com

Shiraz - Zand st.

Linkedin:

kianoosh-soleimanib5a925225

Skills React is 12222 Next js *** HTML *** CSS 3 *** Bootstrap Sass REST API *** Git *** Github *** CI/CD *** Jira Notion Azure CDN Cloudinary ******** Redux **PWA** \$\$\$ Three js Node is

Express

Postman

Mongoose ***

PROFILE

React js Front-end developer with 1+ years of experience in developing projects like CRM, CMS, Blogging sites, Online stores, etc

Self-learner, Teamwork person, Discipline and Punctuality in work, love new challenges, calm under pressure, and following the Cutting-edge technologies to improve me.

EXPERIENCE

Front-end developer, Hillz company, Canada — 2021-Present

Admin panel

This project is a **React-based** admin panel for the management of a car dealership that contains parts like managing vehicles data, handling the finances around negotiating vehicles, **customer relationship management** (CRM), controlling their site and blogs, Multilayer structure for gaining level of a simple customer to buyer, **Role base login** with using a **Token authorization** that user can change their roles base on requirement.

Plink of this project: https://www.hillzusers.com/

Front-end developer, Hillz company, Canada — 2021-Present

Hillz website

Hillz website is a **Static Site Generation (SSG)** website using the **Next js framework** that contains information about their company, forms, packages that they offer to customers(Dealerships), and a blog section for SEO purposes.

I gained the experience of operating and deploying SSG websites in this project.

Plink of this project: https://www.hillzdealer.com/

Front-end developer, Hillz company, Canada — 2021-Present

Hillz dealership website

This project is a Server-Side Rendering (SSR) website using the Next js framework.

In this project, we try to use the ability of SSR in Next js for creating dynamic sections based on what the dealership wants to show to people and their customers. Dynamic parts of this project come from our back-end that uses Node js and Express framework for the back-end server and MySQL for the database. With this config, we can use this project as a Template for other dealerships that like this design for their website and do not require massive changes in the front-end, just creating a table in the database for them and putting their information in that.

Plink of this project: https://www.rteenauto.ca/

Personal information

**** 09395043237

Shiraz - Zand st.

Linkedin:

kianoosh-soleimanib5a925225

Skills

CI/CD

React is Next js *** HTML *** CSS 3 *** Bootstrap Sass *** **REST API** Git *** Github

Jira *** Notion ***

Azure CDN AZURE CDN

Redux 常常常 **PWA**

*** Three is

Node js

Express

Postman Mongo DB ★★★

Mongoose ***

Front-end developer, freelancer, Iran, shiraz — 2021

Bonte takeaway website

Bonte takeaway is a Caffe in shiraz that 5 of my friends established. I tried to mazyar.solo@gmail.com help them share their menu with customers in an easy way.

> This website is generated with **React is framework** and the challenging part of this project was handling the menu images to get from a CDN (Cloudinary) and display it on their site.

> This was a good experience for me because I learned how CDNs works and how we can use them in our projects

Plink of this project: https://bontetakeaway.netlify.app/

EDUCATION

Shiraz University of Technology Degree: Bachelor's degree

Field Of Study: Electrical, Electronics and Communications Engineering

2018-Present

CURRENT POSITION

Lead Front-end Developer in Chadco company in shiraz.